<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>100k on TheDreamIsStillAlive</title>
    <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/tags/100k/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 100k on TheDreamIsStillAlive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/tags/100k/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 29: The Comeback - Setbacks, downswings, and the road ahead</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week29/</guid>
      <description>After a longer-than-expected break from the blog, it&amp;rsquo;s time to shed some light on the reasons behind my silence and share the path forward. Managing a self-hosted blog while dedicating hours to grinding and strategizing on the felt, while still grinding a 9-5, proved more challenging than anticipated. The allure of simply sharing session snapshots on Instagram and Twitter/X vs. crafting detailed blog narratives was more tempting and easier. However, recognizing the value of deeper reflections, I want to find a balance that enriches both my poker journey and your reading experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 20: Navigating New Waters</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week21/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As we roll into week 21 of the bankroll challenge, it&amp;rsquo;s time to reflect on the recent shift in my playing environment and the subsequent challenges that have come with it. The past couple of weeks have been a rollercoaster of transitions, adjustments, and resilience in the face of adversity. After nearly two decades into this journey, the learning never stops, and the battle against variance continues.
Transitioning Platforms Last week marked a change in the 100k bankroll challenge, as I made the decision to migrate from GG and WPT Global over to iPoker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 19: Balancing Act - Grinding and Studying</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week19/</guid>
      <description>As the 19th week of my poker journey folds, I find myself in a phase of diligent progress and introspective learning. Embracing the 100k challenge, my bankroll has reached a healthy $15,497.00.
The Grind: Focusing on NL500 This week&amp;rsquo;s poker grind was concise yet impactful. On Monday, an hour at the NL500 tables brought in a $1,265 profit, while Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s mixed session of NL500 and NL500 ante games padded the bankroll with an additional $1,815.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Frontier: Embarking on the $100k Bankroll Challenge</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week18/</guid>
      <description>As we turn the page from the successful $10,000 bankroll challenge, I find myself at the threshold of a new and more ambitious endeavor - the $100,000 bankroll challenge. This week, not one to rest on past laurels, I&amp;rsquo;ve already dipped my toes into NL500. It&amp;rsquo;s an amusing start as we broke even, dollar for dollar, in the first session. The bankroll now stands at $12,291, marking the beginning of a significant journey ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
