<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trying to survive in the GTO streets on TheDreamIsStillAlive</title>
    <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trying to survive in the GTO streets on TheDreamIsStillAlive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>$10k Challenge Completed: A Journey of Resilience and Growth</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week18-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week18-special/</guid>
      <description>The Finale: Surpassing the $10,000 Bankroll Challenge Today marks a significant milestone. After about 130 hours of grinding across 18 weeks, with disciplined bankroll management and continuous study in the solver, I have successfully completed the $10,000 bankroll challenge. On this day, the 9th of January 2024, a session pushed my cumulative profit to $9,217.80, bringing the starting bankroll for this challenge of $1,000 to a completion total of $10,217.80.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 17: Riding the Variance Wave</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week17/</guid>
      <description>This past week was a vivid illustration of the highs and lows that come with the game. I was actually very close to completing the challenge after the first session of the week. However.. in poker, just as in life, not every session is a smooth ride, and week 17 was the epitome of that.
Session breakdown | Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | Rakeback | Profit incl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 16: The Final Grind of 2023</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week16/</guid>
      <description>As the final cards of 2023 were dealt and the last chips stacked, I found myself reflecting on a great start to my &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; journey throughout the year. Week 16, marking the end of this year&amp;rsquo;s play, was a quieter week with just 3 hours at the tables.
This week&amp;rsquo;s sessions | Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | ------- | ----- | ----- | ---------------- | -------------- | | 2023-12-26 | Tuesday | Grind | 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week15/</guid>
      <description>The ups and downs of NL200 In the spirit of the holiday season, this week&amp;rsquo;s poker journey was akin to a rollercoaster ride through a winter wonderland of variance. Basically, every session was quite swingy. I think overall I rate my execution quite high. However, I did take a few sub-optimal lines in some spots that I haven&amp;rsquo;t studied much due to the low frequency of occurrence, and hence they haven&amp;rsquo;t been prioritised during study sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 14: Riding the Rollercoaster</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week14/</guid>
      <description>This week we had kind of low volume again. Christmas is getting closer, which means there will be more time to grind. Hopefully we can get in some good volume then. Figured it was about time to show the full graph of the challenge so far here on the blog.
The Weekly Roundup Here&amp;rsquo;s how the numbers stacked up for the week:
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | --------- | ----- | ----- | ---------------- | -------------- | | 2023-12-13 | Wednesday | Grind | 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 13: The Leap Forward</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week13/</guid>
      <description>Week 13 will forever be etched in my memory as the week I made a triumphant leap to NL200. It was more than just a step up in stakes; it was a leap in confidence, skill, and mindset.
Session Overview Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of this monumental week:
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | --------- | ----- | ----- | ---------------- | -------------- | | 2023-12-04 | Monday | Grind | 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 12: Navigating the Tides of Fortune</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week12/</guid>
      <description>This week&amp;rsquo;s grind was a testament to the unpredictable nature of the game. It was a week of navigating through the tides, facing challenges, and learning to stay afloat amidst changing fortunes.
Session Overview Here&amp;rsquo;s how the week unfolded:
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | -------- | ----- | ----- | ---------- | -------------- | | 2023-11-28 | Tuesday | Grind | 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 10 &amp; 11: Ups and downs</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week10_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week10_11/</guid>
      <description>Decided to lump together last two weeks, since the volume was so low. It was a bit swingy. From the highs of a triumphant Saturday session to the lows of a tough Monday, it was a couple of weeks filled with intense emotions and valuable learnings.
Session Breakdown Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick overview of how the week unfolded:
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | -------- | ----- | ----- | ---------- | -------------- | | 2023-11-18 | Saturday | Grind | 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 9: A quiet week</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week9/</guid>
      <description>Not much action this week, not much to report on.
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | -------- | ----- | ----- | ---------- | -------------- | | 2023-11-06 | Monday | Grind | 0.80 | NL100 ante | -$79.00 | | 2023-11-06 | Thursday | Grind | 0.87 | NL100 ante | $126.00 | | Totals | | | 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 8:  Riding the Winning Wave in NL100 Ante</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week8/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
Week 8 was all about steady gains and consistent play. After stepping back to NL100, this week was focused on building the bankroll with a series of solid sessions.
The week started off on a positive note on Monday, netting $146 in just over an hour and a half. Thursday followed suit with a $114 win in a little over an hour. The real highlight came on Sunday, where a focused session brought in $279.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7: The Highs And Lows of Moving Up</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week7/</guid>
      <description>Hey,
Week 7 was a rollercoaster, highlighted by the first real shot at a permanent jump in stakes. After a strong start on Monday, boosting my bankroll to $5,100, I took the plunge into the NL200 waters.
The initial dive was promising, with decent wins signaling a good start. However, poker&amp;rsquo;s unpredictable nature struck hard on Thursday. A hefty loss at NL200 forced a retreat back to the familiar grounds of NL100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6: A Momentary Lull</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week6/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone,
Week 6 was like hitting the pause button. Just one session this week, a short stint at the NL100/NL200 ante tables.
Monday&amp;rsquo;s session was a quick dance, but ended up $200 in the red. It was a brief outing, more of a toe-dip than a dive.
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | ------- | ----- | ----- | --------------------- | -------------- | | 2023-10-16 | Monday | Grind | 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5: The Quiet Before the Storm</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week5/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone,
Week 5 was like a ghost town at the poker tables – almost no action. Hit the grind just twice, keeping it short and sweet.
Tuesday was a bit of a downer at NL100 ante, dropping $185. But Thursday flipped the script. Jumped into a mix of NL100 and NL200 ante and came out $855 up – all in just a 0.60-hour session.
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | -------- | ----- | ----- | --------------------- | -------------- | | 2023-10-10 | Tuesday | Grind | 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4: Quality Over Quantity</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week4/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up, peeps
Week 4 was a textbook case of &amp;ldquo;less is more.&amp;rdquo; Dropped the playing hours but upped the game quality. Started with a solid study session in GTOWizard on Monday to sharpen the edges.
Only hit the tables two days this week, but those sessions went very well. Wednesday was a killer day at NL100 ante, locking in a sweet $677 in just over an hour, followed by a steady $50 in the next session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3: Riding The Tides Of Fortune</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week3/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
The third week on my poker journey was a vivid example of the swings in poker. While the week had its share of smaller wins and losses, the standout moments came from a couple of key sessions.
The week had its challenging days, especially early on, but the real highlight was Friday&amp;rsquo;s session. In a remarkable turnaround, I managed to secure a significant win, boosting my confidence and showcasing the potential for success even after a series of tough sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: Enduring The Storm</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week2/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
Week 2 on my poker journey was a lesson in steadiness and patience. I focused mainly on NL100 ante games, navigating the normal ebbs and flows typical at these stakes. This week was a blend of ups and downs, but nothing too dramatic, as the swings were relatively small considering the buy-ins.
| Date | Weekday | Topic | Hours | Stakes | Profit session | | ---------- | --------- | ----- | ----- | ---------- | -------------- | | 2023-09-18 | Monday | Grind | 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1: Navigating Early Setbacks</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/week1/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone,
This week marked the beginning of my poker comeback journey, and let’s just say it’s been a rollercoaster already. I kicked off with a $1,000 deposit, ready to dive back into the grind. But poker, as always, had its own plans.
During my second session, the cards didn’t fall my way. I ended up losing five buy-ins, a setback that definitely tested my resolve. Not one to back down, I jumped into the next session hoping to turn things around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$10 000 Bankroll Challenge</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/challenge/</guid>
      <description>$10 000 Bankroll Challenge Overview To start things off with the new blog and my comeback to poker, I will do the good ol&#39; $10 000 bankroll challenge. The main reason behind doing this is that it gives me motivation since I would be grinding towards a specific goal.
 Starting Bankroll: $1000 Goal: Progressively move up in poker stakes to build the bankroll to $10000.  I guess it is not a fully valid 10k challenge to the purists, since I will be starting with a decently sized bankroll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>Introduction What&amp;rsquo;s up! I&amp;rsquo;m TheDreamIsStillAlive from Norway, and this is my personal poker journal. Allow me to take you on a quick tour through my poker journey.
A Decade in the Poker Trenches From 2007 to 2016, I embarked on a professional poker career that saw me navigating the turbulent streets of the old school online poker era to the newer and more developed theory based game towards the end of my career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Contra vagos Lorem markdownum notam si lintea meque certa en meumque illis, diu fatigant, nec praedae concustodita arcet. Paviunt castris cur errat ventis causa! Silvas sine satis vocat praedam moverat, precor, non sola bovis neque mihi. Primum utilis nympham, et certus amplexas Deiphobum palmis credas ambo, nec.
 Excidit gente, si orat suo quaeque dura Calydon nata? Pars auro post stetit adfusique imis amplexus. Agmina per fabricator mittere Erymanthon habetque tot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://th3dr3amisstillalive.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the blog of TheDreamIsStillAlive, a former professional poker player from Norway.
My Story After a decade-long career (2007-2016) in online poker, I decided to step away from the tables to explore new horizons. My adventures led me through the realms of education and a conventional 9-5 job, but the allure of poker never faded. Even during my hiatus, I managed to claim an unexpected victory at the Norwegian Championship Main Event of Online Poker, reigniting my passion for the game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
